&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，所以我们将通过这个的每个部分。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right, so we're
going to go through each part of this.
解析，所以团队相信源代码是真实的
Parsing, so it's team's belief
that the source code is the true
应用程序的意图，但然后您需要弄清楚这意味着什么。
intention of the application, but then
you need to figure out what that means.
解析很慢。
Parsing is slow.
解析需要花费大量的时间来处理您的10，000行响应应用程序和
Parsing takes a lot of time to take your
like 10,000 line react application and
弄清楚这一切意味着什么。
figure out what it all means.
如果我的意思是你去看看一些精简的代码，看看你是否能找到它。
If I mean you go look at some minified
code and see if you can figure it out.
解析可能会非常慢，在移动设备上可能会慢到每秒1兆字节，对吧？
Parsing can be so slow it can be as slow
as one megabyte a second on mobile, right?
所以如果你的目标是一秒钟的加载时间，比如
So if you're aiming for
that one second load time like
你必须把它交给用户，你必须把它全部解析出来。
you've gotta get it to the user
you've gotta parse it all.
如果你有一个巨大的应用程序就不会发生。
Not gonna happen if you
have a giant application.
因此，一种减少解析时间的方法，再一次，
So one way to reduce the parsing time,
again,
这是金科玉律，对吧？
this is the golden rule thing, right?
是[笑]有更少的代码需要解析。
Is [LAUGH] to have less code to parse.
另一个金科玉律是根据需要进行尽可能多的解析，并且
The other golden rule is to do
as much parsing as you need and
只要你能逃脱惩罚。
as little as you can get away with.
如果有可以稍后解析的东西，我们该怎么做？
If there's things you can parse later,
what do we do?
以后再分析，所以，
Parse it later, so,
V8解析的工作方式是分两个阶段实现的。
the way that V8 parsing works is
it's implemented in two phases.
有急切的解析，这就是你所想的。
There's eager parsing,
which is what you think about.
就像，拿着密码，把它变成ST，我们准备好摇滚了，对吧？
Like, take the code, turn it into the ST,
we're ready to rock, right?
那就是，你想要解析的任何东西，如果你想要解析的话，
That's, anything you think about parsing,
if you think about parsing at all,
就像你想的那样。
like it's what you think of.
然后是懒惰解析，对吧，谁不喜欢懒惰呢？
Then there is lazy parsing, right,
and who doesn't like laziness right?
这就是将拼写错误的单词裸露出来。
Which is to do the misspelled word bare.
当我练习的时候，我也注意到了这一点，并且从未改变过。
When I was practicing I also
noticed that and never changed it.
拼写错误的单词裸露喜欢做你能做的，喜欢做这个如果你需要现在。
Misspelled word bare like do what you can,
like do this if you need now.
任何你现在不需要解析的东西。
Anything that you don't
need to parse right now.
现在不要解析，以后再解析，对吧？
Don't parse it right now,
parse it later, right?
因为这会使您的应用程序更快，所以您无法控制这一点。
Cuz that will make your application
faster, you have no control over this.
这实际上就是
This is effectively what
Chrome正在幕后努力让你的应用程序更快。
Chrome is doing under the hood to try
make your application faster for you.
有很多表演的东西，这是两个人在中间相遇。
With a lot of this performance stuff,
it's two people meeting in the middle.
因此，您所做的事情使您的应用程序更快，
So you doing things that make
your application faster and
它是浏览器供应商做的事情，也使浏览器更快。
it is the browser vendors doing things
to also make the browsers faster.
希望我们能一起跟上Java脚本不断上涨的成本。
And hopefully, together, we can keep
up with the rising cost of JAVA Script.
一般来说，惰性解析是一件好事，对吧？
Generally speaking,
lazy parsing is a good thing, right?
它遵循黄金法则，它是有意义的，它应该是好的。
It follows the golden rules,
it makes sense, it should be good.
因为做更少的工作更快，那么它是如何工作的呢？
Cuz doing less work is faster,
so how does it work?
我们扫描顶层范围，
We scan through the top level scope,
我们解析所有真正要做某事的代码。
we parse all the code that's
actually gonna do something.
就像如果有一个varx等于2，是的，我们需要我们在顶级。
Like if there's a varx equals 2, yeah,
we need that we're in the top level.
但是如果有一些功能，比如那个功能，
But if there's some function,
like that function,
我们不知道什么时候会被叫醒。
we don't know when it's gonna get called.
它可以在Ajax请求后被调用。
It could get called after an ajax request.
我们需要知道它现在做什么的所有细节吗？
Do we need to know all the details
about what it does right now?
不，跳过它，我们稍后再做，我们需要的时候会解析它，让我们开始
No, skip it, we'll do it later, we'll
parse it when we need it, let's get to
现在关键的东西，我们以后再担心其他的东西。
the critical stuff right now and
we'll worry about the other stuff later.
但那可能会咬我们，对吧？
But that could bite us, right?
这里有一个例子。
Here's an example.
好吧，超级，是的，这很天真，但是常量a是1，b是2，很好，对吧？
All right, super, yeah, it's naive but
const a is 1, b is 2, fine, right?
解析这些，我需要这些值。
Parse those, I'm gonna need those values.
然后我遇到了这个函数。
Then I come across this function.
我想，这是一个函数声明，我会跳过它。
I'm like, that's a function declaration,
I'm gonna skip that.
那之后直接发生了什么？
Then what happens directly afterwards?
你需要这个功能。
You need the function.
那么这里真正发生的是什么？&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们
So what really happens here is what?
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We
想想我们懒惰的解析。
think about we lazy parse.
当我们需要一个函数时，我们会急切地解析它。
And when we need a function
we eager parse it.
那么代码中发生了什么呢？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：它没有顺序
So what's happening in that code?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's out of order
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：它坏了，但是
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: It's out of order but
我们也在懒惰地解析它，然后我们必须立即急切地解析它，对吗？
we're also lazy parsing it and then we
have to immediately eager parse it, right?
如果不做事情比做事情快
And if not doing stuff is
faster than doing stuff doing
事情做两次比做一次更慢。
stuff twice is slower
than doing it once right.
所以让我们的代码更快和
So the thing that makes
our code faster and
理所当然的是，就像一个人为的例子，绝对正确。
granted is that like a contrived example,
absolutely right.
但是我们会看到每个人为的例子都有一定的含义
But we'll see that every contrived example
has some amount of implication for
现实世界的应用程序，对吧？
real world applications, right?
它们不是您下次进行代码审查时应该引用的内容，并且
They are not the thing you should cite
next time you do a code review and
你想让某人在事物周围加上圆括号。
you want somebody to add
parentheses around things.
但它们绝对是值得思考的事情
But they are definitely things
that are worth thinking
关于。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么，
about.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So,
如果我们真的把一些东西放在括号里，就像我刚才提到的，
if we actually wrap something in
parentheses, as I mentioned a second ago,
它实际上会得到急切的解析。
it will actually get eager parsed.
这是不是意味着你应该继续
Does that mean that you
should go ahead and
是否将应用程序中的每个函数都放在括号中？
wrap every function in your
application in parentheses?
没有权利？
No right?
知道会发生这种事是有帮助的。
It's helpful to know that happens.
我们称之为微观优化，这是一个很长的花哨词汇
One that's we we call micro-optimatization
which is a long fancy word for
说我想让我的同事恨我。
saying I wanna get my
co-workers to hate me.
但是两个，就像这些东西加起来我就像他们完全一样但是两个，
But two, like these things add up
I'm like they totally do but two,
有一种算法试图帮助你
there's an algorithm that's
trying to help you there and
如果您将每个函数都放在圆括号中，那么您基本上就是在选择退出所有函数
if you wrap every function in parentheses
you're basically opting out of all
懒惰解析，这有点违背了目的。
lazy parsing,
which kind of defeats the purpose.
如果你注意到有问题，它在大多数情况下都能很好地工作，对吗？
It works well most of the time if you
notice there is a problem, right?
理论上你可以这样解决，比那更好，
You could theoretically solve it this way,
better than that,
通常会有图书馆帮助你。
there's usually libraries
that will help you.
这个叫做OptomizeJS，你可以想象它的作用，
This one is called OptomizeJS,
you can imagine what it does,
它在解析的帮助下优化了JS。
it optimizes JS with the help of parsing.
我认为这里的有趣之处在于它将通过
And I think what's kind of interesting
here is that it will go through and
试着弄清楚，而不是每次都要把所有东西都放在括号里，
try to figure out, not every time,
to wrap everything in parentheses,
因为那会很糟糕，但就像是，已知的案例。
because that would be bad,
but like, known cases.
它所做的就是继续前进
What it does is it goes ahead and
解析您的代码以找出一些常见的情况，我必须去哪里，
parses your code to figure out some of the
common cases where did I have to go and
事后立即急于解析，对吧？
immediately eager parse it afterwards,
right?
它会帮你修好一些东西。
And it'll go and
fix some of these things for you.